# William Leondike

I've always been passionate about the code I write. With my exceptional ability to organize, analyze, and adapt; I will continue to develop my programming skills as a full-stack developer each day. I plan to help shape the user experience over the internet, one smile at a time.

Winter Park, Florida (386) 405-4144 billyleondike@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# World of Beer, Orlando —Server

Apr 2019 - Mar 2020 (1 year)

Challenged in a fast-paced environment while delivering fast and efficient service to my customers.

### **All My Sons**, Orlando — Truck Driver

Jun 2018 - Feb 2019 (9 months)

Led a team of movers to deliver fast and efficient results for our customers.

## The Coop, Winter Park

Oct 2016 - Sep 2019 (3 years)

Challenged myself by learning many different positions, bringing the best experience to the customer daily. Willingly hopped between positions to give the best support I could give.

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of Central Florida, Orlando

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

## **Daytona State College**, Daytona Beach — Associates of Arts

Fall 2012 - Spring 2016

General Education

#### **PROJECTS**

# GitHub — https://github.com/WLeondike

Feel free to check out the wonderful projects I've created on my GitHub

#### **SKILLS**

**Analytical Skills** 

Adaptability

**Continuing Education** 

Full-Stack Web Development

**Project Management** 

Time Management

Resource Management

#### **LANGUAGES**

**JavaScript** 

HTML

CSS

**JQuery** 

MySQL